{
  "001": {
    "p-name": "T-Shirt",
    "sizes": ["XS", "S", "M", "L", "XL"],
    "v-ids": ["01", "02"],
    "costs": "\u00a339.90",
    "vid_01": {
      "v-name": "Black",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00101-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00101-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00101-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00101-worn.webp"
    },
    "vid_02": {
      "v-name": "Creme",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00102-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00102-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00102-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00102-worn.webp"
    }
  },
  "002": {
    "p-name": "Denim Jacket",
    "sizes": ["S", "M", "L", "XL", " XXL"],
    "v-ids": ["01"],
    "costs": "\u00a3119.90",
    "vid_01": {
      "v-name": "Black",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00201-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00201-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00201-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00201-worn.webp"
    }
  },
  "003": {
    "p-name": "Jacket",
    "sizes": ["S", "M", "L", "XL", " XXL"],
    "v-ids": ["01", "02", "03", "04"],
    "costs": "\u00a3149.90",
    "vid_01": {
      "v-name": "Red",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00301-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00301-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00301-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00301-worn.webp"
    },
    "vid_02": {
      "v-name": "Blue",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00302-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00302-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00302-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00302-worn.webp"
    },
    "vid_03": {
      "v-name": "Green",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00303-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00303-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00303-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00303-worn.webp"
    },
    "vid_04": {
      "v-name": "Creme",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00304-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00304-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00304-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00304-worn.webp"
    }
  },
  "004": {
    "p-name": "Jogging Pants",
    "sizes": [
      "28-30",
      "30-32",
      "32-34",
      "34-36",
      "36-38",
      "40-44",
      "46-50",
      "52-54",
      "56-60",
      "62-64"
    ],
    "v-ids": ["01", "02", "03"],
    "costs": "\u00a379.90",
    "vid_01": {
      "v-name": "Black",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00401-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00401-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00401-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00401-worn.webp"
    },
    "vid_02": {
      "v-name": "White",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00402-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00402-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00402-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00402-worn.webp"
    },
    "vid_03": {
      "v-name": "Creme",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00403-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00403-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00403-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00403-worn.webp"
    }
  },
  "005": {
    "p-name": "Cargo Pants",
    "sizes": [
      "28-30",
      "30-32",
      "32-34",
      "34-36",
      "36-38",
      "40-44",
      "46-50",
      "52-54",
      "56-60",
      "62-64"
    ],
    "v-ids": ["01", "02"],
    "costs": "\u00a359.90",
    "vid_01": {
      "v-name": "Black",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00501-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00501-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00501-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00501-worn.webp"
    },
    "vid_02": {
      "v-name": "Creme",
      "image-front": "res/clothes/00502-front.webp",
      "image-back": "res/clothes/00502-back.webp",
      "image-extra": "res/clothes/00502-extra.webp",
      "image-worn": "res/clothes/00502-worn.webp"
    }
  }
}
